TRAVIS WITT

524 Wild Oats Dr, Wright City, MO 63390 • 314-202-1897 • TRAVIS.WITT13@GMAIL.COM

Professional Summary

Dependable professional combining customer service skills with technical expertise to resolve complex problems. Excels with strong personal drive, analytical nature, high-productivity, and a record of academic success utilizing excellent interpersonal and communication skills.

Skills

- Windows/MacOS
- Problem Solving Methodologies
- Data Analysis

- Excellent Customer Service
- Web development: HTML, CSS
- ServiceNow Ticket System

Work History

Operations Supervisor, 7/2021 - Present

Supervise staff for clinic and project implementation.

Forecast asset inventory based on future and historical data.

Provide asset management support including creation/maintenance/deletion.

Work with vendors to obtain quotes and price adjustments for returns/replacements.

Support Computer and Software procurement for university online through ServiceNow platform.

Handle shipping and receiving of equipment for hundreds of pieces of equipment daily/weekly.

Train full time staff, contractors on standard practices and process for department.

Maintain daily warehouse for incoming/outgoing freight operations.

Systems Support Analyst, 2/2021 – Present

Select Medical Corporation - Lake St. Louis, MO

Provide Tier 2 technical support to administrative/medical staff.

Manage ticketing via Service-Now.

Install/move/build computers including desktops and laptops.

Document and implement process improvement for several IT practices.

IT Specialist, 8/2020 - 2/2021

United States Department of Agriculture - St. Louis, MO

Request guotes from IT vendors for software/hardware support contracts, as well as IT services contracts.

Communicate with customers on regular basis to ensure customer service is satisfactory and to validate requirements in advance of procurements.

Provide needs analyses to define opportunities for customers to improve business process, consult with customers to identify and specify system requirements, develop overall functional and system requirements for customers, reengineer business processes, and conducts feasibility studies and trade-off analysis.

Technical Support Specialist - Depot, 3/2017 – 7/2020

Washington University in St. Louis – St. Louis, MO

 $\label{provide Tier 2 technical support to administrative staff.} Provide Tier 2 technical support to administrative staff.$

Manage ticketing via Service-Now.

Install/move/build computers including desktops and laptops.

Provide Apple Mac technical support.

Troubleshoot and research potential resolution to issues that arise.

Maintained asset management list of all laptop and desktops.

Provisioned/updated/de-activated accounts in Active Directory.

Managed several file shares including creating folder shares, creating security groups and updating permissions for users.

Support Computer and Software procurement for university online through ServiceNow platform.

Organize and coordinate large clinic project go-lives.

Work with vendors to obtain quotes and price adjustments for returns/replacements.

Support combined efforts of all IT groups to become single point of contact for IT procurement.

Process purchase orders and change orders.

Provide asset management of 1000+ devices being processed through department.

Document and implement process improvement for several IT practices.

Form key relationships with internal and external customers.

Support software asset management through internal database.

Work with internal and external customers to make recommendations based on equipment usage and need.

Handle shipping and receiving of equipment for hundreds of pieces of equipment daily/weekly.

Train student workers on proper process and identify key areas of improvement.

SmartHands Technician, 12/2015 - 3/2017

Ascension Information Services – St. Louis, MO

Provide PC support including Install/Move/Add/Change of computers for clinical and business staff.

Manage ticketing system via Service-Now.

Troubleshoot and research potential resolution to issues that arise.

Provisioned/updated/de-activated accounts in Active Directory.

 $Managed\ several\ file\ shares\ including\ creating\ folder\ shares,\ creating\ security\ groups\ and\ updating\ permissions\ for\ users.$

Started project to implement new asset management program.

Maintained asset management database of all laptops, desktops, tablets, and printers.

Network Analyst Intern, 7/2014 - 2/2015

Regional Justice Information Service (REJIS) Commission – St. Louis, MO

Assist Network Analysts in desktop, network, and remote support for various government and law enforcement agencies around St. Louis Metropolitan area.

Information Systems Technician Second Class, 12/2008 – 7/2012

United States Navy - San Diego, CA

Maintain 100% inventory and accountability for classified and non-classified material.

Supervised work center technicians.

Troubleshoot multiple network circuits providing critical network connectivity via ship and shore to multiple government/military agencies.

Coordinated and ran multiple training sessions of communications equipment.

Education

Bachelor of Science, Information Technology: 2015 **Lindenwood University –** St. Charles, MO

GPA: 3.97

Certifications

Full Stack Web Development Boot Camp: 2022 Washington University in St. Louis – St. Louis, MO In Progess